<?xml version="1.1" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<databaseChangeLog xmlns="http://www.liquibase.org/xml/ns/dbchangelog" xmlns:ext="http://www.liquibase.org/xml/ns/dbchangelog-ext" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.liquibase.org/xml/ns/dbchangelog-ext http://www.liquibase.org/xml/ns/dbchangelog/dbchangelog-ext.xsd http://www.liquibase.org/xml/ns/dbchangelog http://www.liquibase.org/xml/ns/dbchangelog/dbchangelog-latest.xsd">
    <changeSet author="MRINNE (generated)" id="1749118171326-1">
        <insert tableName="SUPPORT_CASE">
            <column name="CASE_ID" valueNumeric="2"/>
            <column name="DESCRIPTION" value="Product: Smart Coffee Maker (Model: BREW-SMART 3000)&#10;Date of Purchase: February 15, 2024&#10;Case Opened: June 15, 2024&#10;Issue Description:&#10;The customer reported that the coffee maker’s touchscreen display was unresponsive after a recent software update. The machine brews coffee as programmed but the screen does not respond to touch commands, making it difficult to adjust settings or select brew options.&#10;Steps Taken by Customer:&#10;Unplugged the coffee maker for 10 minutes and restarted it.&#10;Attempted to recalibrate the touchscreen using the instructions in the manual.&#10;Ensured the software update was fully installed by checking the machine’s settings menu (via physical buttons).&#10;Additional Notes:&#10;Product is within the 1-year warranty period.&#10;No physical damage or spills reported.&#10;Customer is highly satisfied with the product otherwise and uses it daily.&#10;Requested Resolution:&#10;The customer requested assistance in resolving the touchscreen issue and ensuring the coffee maker functions as expected.&#10;Assigned Support Agent: Alex Martinez&#10;Status: Closed | Resolved&#10;Resolution Details:&#10;After reviewing the case, the support agent determined that the issue was caused by a minor software glitch during the update. The agent provided the customer with a step-by-step guide to perform a factory reset, which resolved the touchscreen unresponsiveness. The customer confirmed that the display is now fully functional and they can adjust settings without issue."/>
        </insert>
        <insert tableName="SUPPORT_CASE">
            <column name="CASE_ID" valueNumeric="4"/>
            <column name="DESCRIPTION" value="Product: High-Speed Blender (Model: BLEND-MAX 5000)&#10;Date of Purchase: April 10, 2024&#10;Case Opened: June 25, 2024&#10;Issue Description:&#10;The customer reported that the blender’s motor was making an unusual grinding noise during operation, particularly when blending frozen fruits or ice. The noise started recently and seemed to be getting louder with each use.&#10;Steps Taken by Customer:&#10;Checked for any loose parts or debris in the blender jar.&#10;Ensured the blender was assembled correctly and the blade was securely attached.&#10;Tried blending softer ingredients (e.g., bananas, yogurt) to see if the noise persisted.&#10;Additional Notes:&#10;Product is within the 2-year warranty period.&#10;No visible damage or leaks reported.&#10;Customer uses the blender daily for smoothies and soups.&#10;Requested Resolution:&#10;The customer requested assistance in diagnosing the issue and a potential repair or replacement if necessary.&#10;Assigned Support Agent: Claire Thompson&#10;Status: Closed | Resolved&#10;Resolution Details:&#10;The support agent suspected the issue might be related to the motor bearings or blade alignment. After gathering more details, the agent arranged for a replacement blender to be shipped to the customer under warranty. The customer was provided with a prepaid return label to send back the defective unit.&#10;The replacement blender arrived within 3 business days, and the customer confirmed it was working perfectly without any unusual noises. The agent also shared maintenance tips, such as avoiding overloading the blender and regularly cleaning the blade assembly."/>
        </insert>
        <insert tableName="SUPPORT_CASE">
            <column name="CASE_ID" valueNumeric="1"/>
            <column name="DESCRIPTION" value="Product: Smart Air Purifier (Model: PURE-AIR 7000)&#10;Date of Purchase: September 5, 2023&#10;Case Opened: July 3, 2024&#10;Issue Description:&#10;The customer reported that the air purifier’s filter replacement indicator light was continuously on, even after installing a new filter. The purifier functions normally, but the indicator light remains lit, which is confusing and concerning.&#10;Steps Taken by Customer:&#10;Replaced the filter with a genuine, compatible filter from the manufacturer.&#10;Reset the air purifier by unplugging it for 5 minutes and then plugging it back in.&#10;Checked the user manual for instructions on resetting the filter indicator, but the issue persisted.&#10;Additional Notes:&#10;Product is within the 2-year warranty period.&#10;No error codes or unusual noises reported.&#10;Customer uses the air purifier daily in their living room.&#10;Requested Resolution:&#10;The customer requested assistance in resolving the filter indicator issue and ensuring the purifier is functioning correctly.&#10;Assigned Support Agent: Ryan Patel&#10;Status: Closed | Resolved&#10;Resolution Details:&#10;The support agent identified that the issue was likely due to a sensor malfunction. After verifying the warranty status, the agent arranged for a replacement air purifier to be shipped to the customer. The customer was provided with a prepaid return label to send back the defective unit.&#10;The replacement air purifier arrived within 4 business days, and the customer confirmed that the filter indicator light was functioning correctly. The agent also provided instructions on how to manually reset the filter indicator in the future, should the issue arise again."/>
        </insert>
        <insert tableName="SUPPORT_CASE">
            <column name="CASE_ID" valueNumeric="3"/>
            <column name="DESCRIPTION" value="Product: Bluetooth Wireless Earbuds (Model: SOUND-BUDS PRO)&#10;Date of Purchase: March 20, 2024&#10;Case Opened: June 20, 2024&#10;Issue Description:&#10;The customer reported that one of the earbuds (right earbud) was not connecting to their phone, even though the left earbud and charging case were functioning properly. The right earbud would not pair independently or as part of the set.&#10;Steps Taken by Customer:&#10;Reset the earbuds by placing them in the charging case and holding the pairing button for 10 seconds.&#10;Tried pairing the earbuds with multiple devices (phone, laptop, tablet).&#10;Ensured the earbuds were fully charged before attempting to pair.&#10;Additional Notes:&#10;Product is within the 1-year warranty period.&#10;No physical damage or water exposure reported.&#10;Customer uses the earbuds daily for work calls and music.&#10;Requested Resolution:&#10;The customer requested assistance in resolving the connection issue or a replacement if necessary.&#10;Assigned Support Agent: Jordan Lee&#10;Status: Closed | Resolved&#10;Resolution Details:&#10;The support agent guided the customer through a detailed troubleshooting process, which included:&#10;Forgetting the earbuds from all paired devices.&#10;Placing the earbuds back in the case and closing the lid for 1 minute.&#10;Opening the lid and immediately attempting to pair again.&#10;This process successfully reconnected the right earbud, and the customer confirmed both earbuds were working seamlessly. The agent also provided tips on maintaining a stable Bluetooth connection, such as keeping the earbuds close to the device and avoiding interference from other electronics."/>
        </insert>
    </changeSet>
</databaseChangeLog>
